erate.co.il 2019-05-10

# 1.

1. Overview
This privacy policy sets out how eRate(c) Corporation uses, protects and treats any information
that eRate(c) Corporation collects and receives, including information related to your use of the
eRate(c) Web site (the “Site”) or the eRate(c)s ad serving servers either by us or on behalf of
our clients. The eRate(c) ad serving business is operated by eRate(c) Corporation and/or by its
sister and/or affiliates companies worldwide. eRate(c) is committed to ensure that your privacy
is protected. Should you provide certain personal information from which you can be identified
when using the Site, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with the terms
and conditions of this privacy policy. Personal information is information about you that is
personally identifiable like your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, company name
and information that is not otherwise publicly available. eRate(c) may change this policy from
time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that
you are happy with any changes. In addition when the Privacy Policy is changed we will update
the last change time on the “site” http://www.erate.co.il
2. Information collection and use
• If you register with eRate(c) as Publisher or Advertiser or Agency or
Network:
When you register with us you may be asked for some personal information such as,
but not limited to, name, address, company name, e-mail address, telephone number.
We may also store your IP address to prevent any fraudulent access to your account.
We use your data to communicate with you within your business activity with us and
for billing purposes. We do not disclose any of your personal data to any third party.
However, in case of a legal and proper Court Order requiring us to divulge your
information we may be obliged to provide your information. Other than as required
by a Court order, the only people authorized to view your contact or billing
information are authorized employees of eRate(c) and/or eRate(c) sister companies,
acting within the scope of their duties. We may use cookie to keep track of your
activity on the Site.
• If you are an Internet user
You receive advertising ads served by our clients: In the process of providing online
advertising, eRate(c) does not collect any personally identifiable data, which is data
collected with an intention to identify and contact a person such as name, address,
telephone number or e-mail address (“PII”) from Internet users with respect to such
online advertising products. We use technology such as cookies and web beacons to
collect general data on the performance of our colleges advertising campaigns so we
can report aggregated results. This data is collected on an anonymous and nonpersonally
identifiable basis. The non-personally identifiable information that
eRate(c) collects may include, as an example, browser types, operating systems,
domain names, access dates and times, referring website addresses, online
transactions and browsing and search activity “Non-PII”.
eRate(c) collects data on behalf of our clients using eRate(c) cookie technology.
When doing this, a persistent browser cookie is placed on the visitor’s computer that
will allow for the collection and storing of certain types of activity.

3. Information sharing and disclosure
eRate(c) may make available to our clients Internet users non-personal information to better
target their advertisements, for aggregate collection and reporting for clients and their partners
and for the improvement of our ad serving system. In addition, we may combine anonymous
information collected using our ad serving technology with that of third parties and partners for
ad targeting and behavior modeling purposes.
eRate(c) may also share collected information in
the following circumstances: * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to
investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations
involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of eRate(c)’s terms of
use, or as otherwise required by law. * We transfer information about you if eRate(c) is acquired
by or merged with another company.
In this event, eRate(c) will notify you before information
about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. The notice will be
published on this page.
4. Cookies
A cookie is a small file generated on a visitor’s computer that allows us to gather non-personal
data to target advertisements and track anonymous activity on this or other Web sites. Most Web
browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to
decline cookies if you prefer. When an internet user views an advertisement served by eRate(c)
for one of our clients we may collect and store information including the visitor’s anonymous
cookie identifier, the advertisement shown to that visitor and certain geographic data. Some of
our clients or their partners may send us anonymous data so that we may better target
advertisements or determine if our advertisements have resulted in certain actions by the visitor.
At no time does eRate(c) store any information from our clients that would allow us to
individually identify those that view our advertisements. Overall, cookies allow our clients the
ability to provide a better advertising experience for their visitors. A cookie in no way gives us
access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share
with us.
5. Web beacons
A Web beacon, or pixel, is a piece of HTML code placed onto a Web page or into an
advertisement. When your Web browser loads a Web page or an advertisement is displayed, and
a Web beacon is present, it sends a request to our servers. Our clients employ our beacons on
Web pages and in advertisements to measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns, to
show specific advertisements to visitors based on anonymous data present in their cookie and to
determine the usage pattern of ad viewers that visit their Web pages or those of their partners.
The data collected is anonymous and is returned to our servers for processing and reporting.
6. Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised
access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial
procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

7. Opt-Out
eRate(c) is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors and providing privacy options for
those that view advertisements served through our system. We offer the ability to opt out of our
eRate(c) Cookie information system by implementing an eRate(c) Opt-Out cookie on your Web
browser. Using the eRate(c) Opt Out Cookie will not prevent advertisements served through
eRate(c) from being presented to you but will stop the collection and storing of data regarding
your visit while being served an advertisement by one of our clients. To opt-out, please use the
opt-out link in our site, found in about us page.
8. Links to other web sites
Our Web site may contain links to enable you to visit other Web sites of interest easily.
However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have
any control over that other Web site. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and
privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not
governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy
statement applicable to the Web site in question.
9. Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
By email: support@erate.co.il
By postal mail: eRate(c) David Hamelech 1, Hertzlya, Israel
This policy is effective from March 16, 2012
